(Hawking:)Sheldon, you're too brilliant.
(Amy:)How can you feel bad
(Amy:)if Stephen Hawking says
you're brilliant?
(Sheldon:)I can't.
(Sheldon:)Thank you, Professor Hawking.
(Sheldon:)You are a gift to mankind.
(Sheldon:)There should be statues
of you everywhere.
(Sheldon:)You know, the Lincoln Memorial
has a big chair.
(Sheldon:)We could swap you right in.
(Hawking:)I always thought a motorized toy
of me would be cool.
What a wonderful idea!
(Sheldon:)How does this man
not have a Nobel?
(Leonard:)Do not tell Wolowitz.
Way ahead of you.
(Ellen:)A new study came out,
and it said that laughing
(Ellen:)makes your brain work better.
(Ellen:)And I know that's true
because laughing
has made me the "smartiest."
(Ellen:)Although, on the other hand,
(Ellen:)babies laugh a lot,
and they're dumb.
(Sheldon:)Do people know about her?
'Cause she's delightful.